Association for Research and Enlightenment Collection
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
- Publications, 1931 2015
  - Box 6
    - A.R.E. News, 1983; Folder 6:11; Brittell, Katherine A.; Boyle, Richard; Redman, Velva A.; January, 1983 -New Era Begins for Cayce Remedies -Home Health Products Now on Manufacturing Assembly Line -New Study Groups -Headquarters 1983 Conference Calendar -Astrology Research Project -ARE Endowment Funds are Growing -Hugh Lynn: A Friend Remembered (Meredith Puryear, Gladys McGarey, M.D., Michael Dennis, Ph.D., Robert Jeffries, Ph.D., Robert Witt, M.Ed., Ursula Jahoda) -We Are the ARE (Hugh Lynn Cayce Tape) -ARE Trek to Mt. Everest -Field Programs -Join Us in Meditation: Opportunity February, 1983 -Field Volunteer Services: Call on us anytime! -Lend a Hand... (Christopher Fazel) -Motivating the Spirit in Business (Richard Peterson) -1983 Wilderness Retreats -Camp Reflections: The Ongoing Work of Love -ARE Camp: "First star on the right and straight on 'til morning! (Judith Stevens) -ARE Green Woods School: A Dream That Can Come True -Chairman of Board's Life Validates Reading (Erik Jensen) -Over the Wall -March Field Programs -The Seabeck Spring Retreat and Palestine Symposium (Miriam Kent) -Join Us in Meditation: Day and Night -New Study Groups March, 1983 -New Directions for Printing Manager: An Interview with Linda Betts -benefit concert for the Braille Library -The ARE Requests Your Board Nominee Suggestions (Charles Thomas Cayce) -Highlights: Summer Conferences, 1982, Selected Insights and Shared Impressions (Sharon James, Executive Secretary, Enlightenment Services Division) -The Ethics of Emergence (David Spangler) -Life After Birth (Gladys McGarey) -Forgiveness Is the Key to Happiness (Gerald Jampolsky) -The Greater Cosmos (Leon Edward Wright) -Self-Regulation: Development of Willpower (Norman Shealy) -Gifts on the Path: The Dwarf, the Enchanter and the Royal Self (Harmon Bro) -Other Worlds, Other Lives: The Hebrew View of Reincarnation (Herbert Weiner) -The Pooled Income Fund -Recollections: Hugh Lynn Cayce -Join Us in Meditation: God, the Father, and His Manifestations in the Earth -New Study Groups -April Field Programs -Attend a Major Regional Symposium in Washington, D.C., Chicago, or Hartford (Miriam Kent) April, 1983 -ARE Selects Vice-President (Russell E. Dyke) -Membership Responses Aid in Program Planning: Results of Field Programming Research Report (Sharon James) -A Healing Experience Gives ARE a Prayer Services Coordinator: An Interview with Karla La Voie -We Can Make a Difference! Prayer Services - 1983 (Karla La Voie) -Join Us in Meditation: Desire -A Dear Friend and Helper: In Memoriam: Lester Babcoke -ARE's Seal is Displayed in Masthead -Highlights from ARE Board of Trustee's Meeting (Erik Jensen) -ARE Now Recruiting Volunteers for Work-Scholarship Program -Spotlighting Harmon Bro and the Course: The Possible You (Miriam Kent) -May Field Programs -Congress: An Opportunity for Service (Jim Bloomquist, Darlene Bodner) -Leadership Training Set for June May, 1983 -Arch Ogden, President of ECF Board, Announces a Celebration of Gladys Davis's 60th ARE Anniversary -Meet the Winners! Your Favorite Study Group Leaders -Over the Wall: How Could We Refuse? -New Study Groups -Tithing with Time: Serving the Elderly in a Convalescent Home or Hospital -First Printing of The Edgar Cayce Primer Is a Sellout -Bring ARE Books to Your Community Through a Library Display -June and July Field Symposia -Spotlighting Judith Stevens and the Course: Abundance is Yours -Highlights from ARE Board of Trustees Meeting (Erik Jensen) -ARE Tour Visits China in August -What God Can Do: Following Through Brings Light to Others (Theresa Cole) -Join Us in Meditation: Destiny of the Mind June, 1983 -ARE Library Receives Cox Collection (Robert Cox) -Robert Cox, Bibliophile - and His Association with the ARE: An interview with Lois Cox, Robert's sister; former teacher and principal for 40 years of the Maryland School for the Blind -Lois Cox Recalls Edgar Cayce's Sunday School Class -Position Opening: Youth Activities Manager -Using Your Face to Face Supplement -Northern Virginia Challenges You: Our Children and Our Future Are in Our Hands -A Chance Meeting with Strangers (George and Mary Haselton, Regional Representatives for New Hampshire and Vermont -Regional Area Representatives Serve Members (Lyn Costaldo) -New Study Groups -Eight Days in Paradise: An ARE Wilderness Trip to the Virgin Islands (Adelaide Crockett, ARE Library Clerk) -Spirit in Business (Richard Peterson, Manager, Conference Services) -Teachings for Our Times: Gurdijeff and Cayce -Dr. William McGarey and Holistic Healing -Join Us in Meditation: Destiny of the Body -An Update on ARE's Health Care Professionals Program July, 1983 -1983 Annual Giving: Halfway There (Glenn Sanderfur) -Correctional Institutions Express Appreciation for ARE Prison Program: New Plans Underway -ARE Tour Members to Explore Mexico -Be Content not Satisfied: A Circulating File from The Quotes and Similes Series -Gifted Guide to the Inner Self: Carol Bush (Lise Stryker, Headquarters Registrar) -A Portrait of Gertrude and Edgar Cayce (Harriet Kronick) -Edgar Cayce's Dream of His Future Bride -Gladys Davis Works With Her Ideal -What One Person Can Do: Update of the Field Instructor Program -On the Road... (Christopher Fazel, ARE Headquarters Study Group Starter) -New Study Groups -Spirit in Business (Richard Peterson) -Join Us in Meditation: Destiny of the Soul -In Memoriam: Egerton Sykes August, 1983 -Special Guests Selected for Gladys Davis' Anniversary Party (Hillery E. Poole, Riley E. Simmons, Harold G. Allen, Harold Reilly, Robert A. Adriance, J. Everett Irion) -Visitor Center Introduces ARE to Thousands (Karen Fili, Communications Assistant) -Behind the Scenes (Joan Grasser, Manager, Financial Services; Patti Morrissey, Supervisor, Purchasing, Buildings and Grounds) -Spirit in Business: Learning a Lesson from Layoff (Richard Peterson) -1983 Business Conference -September Field Programs -Dream Provides Stepping-Stones (Kevin F. Coughlin, Martha's Vineyard, Mass. Study Group No. 1) -Dream Shields (Henry Reed, Ph.D.) -Be ARE's Guest at Gladys Davis' Party -Highlights from ARE Board of Trustees Meeting (Erik Jensen) -Make the Work Come Alive: An Interview with Gerald Matlin, Board member and Chairman of the Long-Range Planning Committee -Begin Your New Year in an Old Country: Join the ARE Egypt Tour (Norrene Leary, ARE Tour Director) -Join Us in Meditation: Glory September, 1983 -Mae Gimbert St. Clair, Originator of Readings Research Department, Honored During Congress Week -ARE Seeks Magazine Project Manager -Spotlighting Lynn Sparrow and the Course: Remembering Your Past Lives (Miriam Kent) -October Field Programs -Lesley Laraby Boykin, Pediatric Speech Pathologist, and Her Experiences with the Readings -My Experiences While Writing the Commentary to the Circulating File: Stuttering (Lesley Laraby Boykin) -Contemporary Authors Back Readings Concepts: George Leonard, Gay Luce, Jess Stearn, Pir Vilayat Inayat Khan, Fritjof Capra share in Field Symposia (Sharon James) -Psychical Research at ARE: First Report -Spirit in Business: A More Excellent Way (Richard Peterson) -Join Us in Meditation: Knowledge October, 1983 -ARE President Presents New Dream Course: An Interview with Charles Thomas Cayce (Miriam Kent) -Service Unto Our Neighbor: A Report of 1983 ARE Congress (Jim Bloomquist) -1984 New Year's Conference: The Quest for Vision: Personal and Planetary (Cathy Lamb, Headquarters Conference Coordinator) -Over the Wall -Meet You in Saskatchewan -New Study Groups -Happy 25th Birthday, Dallas Council! -New Circulating File on Disorders of the Heart -ARE Outreach: Reaching Out to Other Seekers -November Field Programs -J. Everett Irion and Lynn Sparrow Present Seminar: Making the Bible Come Alive in Your Life -A Conversation with J. Everett Irion (Amanda Wakester) -Spirit in Business (Richard Peterson) -Join Us in Meditation: Wisdom November, 1983 -Edgar Cayce's Theories Applied in Holistic Nursing -How ARE Selects Quality Books (Phyllis Embleton) -Health Care Professionals: How to work with your health problem, Circulating Files and an ARE Health Care Professional -Friends of ARE Camp Seek New Members -ARE Clinic Holds Annual Medical Symposium on Holistic Healing -A Prison Valedictorian Speaks... -New Study Group -Letters of Thanks -Spirit in Business: The Creative Principle of Oneness (Richard Peterson) -Celebrate Christmas as a Member of the ARE Family -Join Us in Meditation: Happiness December, 1983 -ARE Members Share Ideas of Aiding Elderly -The Twelve Days of Christmas: A Spiritual Journey -Fruits of the Spirit: A Circulating File from The quotes and Similes Series, compiled by Mae Gimbert St. Clair -Field Programs -Stepping Back into History to Become Up to Date: In 1937, Hugh Lynn Cayce Spelled Out the Purpose of ARE Study Groups (Judith Stevens) -New Study Groups -Over the Wall (Judith Stevens) -Pen Pal Needed -The Most Beautiful Angel (Theresa Cole)
    - A.R.E. News, 1984; Folder 6:12; Brittell, Katherine A.; Redman, Velva A.; March, 1984 -Magazine Scheduled for Fall -An Interview with New Magazine Editor - A. Robert Smith -In Praise of Volunteers -The Music and the Flower Lady (Excerpt from Edgar Cayce Reading 5122) -The Small Hand of Jesus (Veda Adams, ARE Member, McAllen, Texas) -A Camper's Eye View -A Thank-You Note to Members (Charles Thomas Cayce) -A Tribute: Grethe Tedrick: Serves ARE and California Community for over Two Decades (Judith Stevens) -New Study Groups -Volunteer World Travelers on Tour (Bill and Elsie Sechrist) -Traveling in His Light (Jean Barker, ARE Field Instructor, Miami -Field Conferences: A Family Affair (Sharon James, Field Conference Design Coordinator; Pepin family) -Easter Retreat to Focus on Inner Life -Circulating Files Benefit Members -Spirit in Business: The Business Readings (Richard Peterson) -April Field Programs April, 1984 -1984 Congress To Focus on Jesus as Pattern (Darlene Bodnar, 1984 Congress Chairperson) -Monthly Healthcare Reports Center on Common Concerns -Jesus' Last Week -We Are ARE's Soul (Kathleen Meade, Prayer Program Coordinator) -One Man's Vision: An Interview with Artist Francis Sporer (Katherine A. Brittell) -Portraying Your Life Purposes Through Art -Highlights from the ARE Board Meeting (Erik Jensen) -Last Words of Convict Echo Christ (Judith Stevens) -Five Members Receive Tuition-Free Pass to '84 Conferences -Readings Help Father Overcome Loss: A Letter to ARE President, Charles Thomas Cayce -Work / Scholarship Program Available to Volunteers -Easter Retreat -May Headquarters Conferences -May Field Programs -Leadership Training Seminar Set for June May, 1984 -Harmon Bro Featured Speaker at Congress -Clinical Studies Planned for Cayce Remedies - Cooperating Physicians Sought -Spirit in Business: Can I Skip This Challenge? (Richard Peterson) -There Is a Place Where You Are Needed -Letters Reveal Loving Relationship (Sarah Cayce Hesson and Edgar Cayce; Katherine Brittell) -Celebration Honors Original Member of First Study Group (Helen Ellington) -A Flower Grows in New York City (New York Study Group No. 23) -Over the Wall: Study Group Members Visit Texas Prison (Judith Stevens) -Participate in Prayer Experiment (Kathleen Meade) -June Headquarters Conferences -June Field Programs June, 1984 -Edgar Cayce Film Festivals Are a Big Hit (Edith Wilson, Coordinator, Field Support Services) -Bermuda Triangle Author Gives Unique Gift to Library (Charles Berlitz) -In Memoriam: Gina Cerminara -Cayce's Advice - Each One Reach One - Still Sound (Marilyn Peterson, Director of Membership Services -ARE 53rd Congress: What Shall We Do with this Man Called Jesus? -Group Researches Work Readings -Who Are Today's Children? (Lois Gateney, Coordinator, Youth Activities) -Juvenile Outreach Program Launched: Cayce Books Delivered -A Visit to a Detention Home (Wayne Emley, Coordinator, Over the Wall Program -Needy Members Helped -In Memoriam: Sarah Cayce Hesson -Home Study Course Develops Awareness of Past Lives -Want a Piece of the Sunshine State? -Optimism is Focus of Ohio Retreat -Join Us in Meditation: Fellowship -July Headquarters Conferences July, 1984 -Dr. Windsor, ECF Vice-President Discusses Current Projects -Invitation to a New Research Project: Obtaining Guidance from Dreams -Highlights from the ARE Board Meeting (Erik Jensen) -Over the Wall Prison Program: Juvenile Detention Home Outreach Project Soars -A Friendship Too Valuable to Lose: By A Member -Sharing-Thru-Giving Support Less than Last Year (Glenn Sanderfur) -ARE Receives National Award (Best in Catalogs 1984 Finalist) -Spirit in Business: The Ideal (Richard Peterson) -A Letter: Collective Prayer Aids Sisters Throughout Death Experience -July / August Wilderness Retreats -August Headquarters Conferences -Join Us in Meditation: Patience August, 1984 -ARE Congress Largest in Three Years -First Issue of Magazine to Appear Next Month -The Seeker Answers: Excerpt from Harmon Bro's Introduction to Congress -Congress Honors Three Members (Al Mann, Esther Ham, Everett Irion) -Candid Shots of Congress -Health Care Report Continues as Special Membership Benefit -ARE Wilderness Retreats -Cayce Formula Works! -First Section of Prayer / Healing Workbook Now Available -September Headquarters Conferences -The Way Home... Excerpts from a Congress talk on ARE's Prison Program, and the first videotaped prison Study Group (Judith Stevens) -Fall Field Programs -Join Us in Meditation: The Open Door -Leadership Training Seminar Set for September ARE Headquarters
  - Box 7
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1966 1967; Folder 7:1; Sugrue, Thomas; Robinson, Lytle; Cayce, Edgar; Foster, Lewis A., Jr.; Montgomery, Ruth; Clapp, Robert O.; Berkeley, Edmund; Puryear, Herbert; Cerminara, Gina; Nichols, Cecil; Irion, J. Everett; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Bogardus, Steven; Dankers, Naomi; Richardson, A. Jane; Martin, Carol Anne; Grose, Carol; Adriance, Robert; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Bush, Grace; Coblentz, Stanton; Delaney, Dudley; Dommeyer, Fred; Harvey, Dan; Jacob, Lindsay; Kimes, R.E.; Klemm, Roland; Kohr, Richard; McGarey, William; Van Meter, Paula; Miller, Mary Lou; Secundus, Caius P.C.; Shelley, Violet; Sigma, Rho; Spickler, Betty; Taylor, John
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1968 1969; Folder 7:2; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Boykin, Louis; Brewster, Joyce; Brunner, Lucille; Carlson, Vada; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Church, W.H.; Coates, William; Cohen, Allen; Haller, Genevieve; Hardy, Belva; Hewitt, Barbara; Johnson, Raynor; Johnson, Zoe; Kidd, Worth; Kirkland, Elithe; Kirkland, Roy, D.O.; Klemm, Roland; Kozikowski, John; Krajenke, Robert; Lamsa, George; Magee, John G.; McGarey, William; Mikulak, Maxim; Miller, Noah; Miller, Shane; Nichols, Cecil; Plym, D.L.; Puryear, Herbert; Quest, Linda; Robinson, Lytle; Shelley, Violet; Sherman, Margaret; Sugrue, Thomas; Thomas, Ahrcel; Wild, Warren; Windsor, James; Woodward, Mary Ann
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1970 1971; Folder 7:3; Aiken, Warren R.; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Baraff, Carol; Bjork, Ray; Blaney, Marion; Boykin, Louis; Breitenbeck, Sister Thomas; Brewster, Joyce; Busch, Ernestine; Church, W.H.; Duncan, Mary; Fitch, Reverend Joseph; Henderson Cynthia; Hollings, George; Huntress, Diana; Huson, Hobart; Irion, J. Everett; Jett, Margaret; Johnson, Mary; Johnson, Tom; Jones, Janet; Kerr, Reverend Donald; Kidd, Worth; Klausner, Margot; Klemm, Roland; Lamsa, George; Landers, Olive; Lansford, Fred; Lishnoff, Mollye; Markham, Lucia; McGarey, Gladys; Price, Edith; Propes, Warren; Quest, Linda; Robinson, Lytle; Shaffranke, Rolf; Schneller, Sibyl; Sherman, Margaret; Stryker, Linda; Sugrue, Thomas; Tenhaeff, W.H.C.; Trop, June; Ware, Winthrop; Wolfe, Mary
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1971 1972; Folder 7:4; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Church, W.H.; Clapp, Robert O.; Furst, Jeffrey; Gilling, Lucille; Goodman, Jeffrey; Gorman, Carl; Hamilton, Nancy; Hattersley, Ralph; Johnson, Mary; Krajenke, Robert; Krippner, Stanley; Goldsmith, M.; Zirinsky, K.; Lieberman, Daniel; McGarey, William; Norris, Margaret; O'Donnell, Robert; Puryear, Meredith; Quest, Linda; Rehrig, Julie; Remke, Samuel; Smith, Peter; St. Clair, Mae Gimbert; Tiller, William; Viewig, Mark
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1972 1973; Folder 7:5; Adamenko, Victor; A.M.R.; Apelman, Martin; Ardinger, Dennis; Ballard, Juliet Brooke; Busch, Ernestine; Carley, Ken; Carlson, Vada; Cayce, Charles Thomas; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Church, W.H.; Davidson, Frederick; Davidson, Janis; Doumas, Judy; Drummond, Richard; Fields, Virginia; Hamilton, Nancy; Humann, Harvey; Johnson, Mary; Johnson, Tom; Baraff, Carol; Krippner, Stanley; Zeichmer, S.; Lehner, Mark; Lidstrom, Paul; McGarey, William; Norment, Owen; O'Malley, George; Quest, Linda; Raikov, Vladimir; Ray, Margaret; Scott, Cora; Sklar, Dusty; Steinhart, Lawrence; Stuart, Sharon; Thurston, Mark; Tomlin, Mary; Warner, Vicki; Weed, Bill; Weed, Theresa; Wray, James
  - Box 8
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1974 1975; Folder 8:1; Beck, Pluma; Blake, Hudson; Carley, Ken; Cayce, Charles Thomas; Thurston, Mark; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Church, W.H.; Dickman, Thomas; Doumas, Judy; Drummond, Richard; Friedman, Father Elias; Green, Elmer; Green, Alyce; Kessler, Renee; McGarey, William; Price, Edith; Puryear, Herbert; Reed, Henry; Rinehart, Iverne C.; Runnels, Douglas; Shelley, Violet; Sinex, Charles; Sparrow, Gregory Scott; Spears, Ralph; Sutton, J.F.; Zink, David
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1975 1976; Folder 8:2; Bullard, Barbara; Carley, Ken; Church, W.H.; Clapp, Robert O.; Emerson, J. Norman; Ida, Edward; Jeffries, Robert; Kohr, Richard; McGarey, William; Miller, Shane; Oakes, Jerry; Quest, Linda; Sides, Ralph; Beauchamp, R.; Sloan, E.; Sigma, Rho; Thurston, Mark; Zink, David
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1976 1977; Folder 8:3; Alt, Bonnie; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Church, W.H.; Davidson, Frederick; Davidson, Janis; Davis, Alma; Devorn, Oleg J.; Drummond, Richard; Dunn, Gregory; Kohr, Richard; Krajenke, Robert; Matlin, Gerald; Matlin, Sloane E.; McArthur, Bruce; McDowell, Helen; McGarey, William; Michel, Emory; Pagano, John; Popa, Marcia; Puryear, Herbert; Richards, Douglas; Shealy, Norman; Sutton, J.F.; Thurston, Mark
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1978 1979; Folder 8:4; Baker, Jim; Behra, Sue; Bennett, Stephanie; Cayce, Charles Thomas; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Church, W.H.; Clement, Shirley; Haller, Genevieve; Henderson, Elizabeth; Howell, Faith; Hruska, Elaine; Krajenke, Robert; McArthur, Bruce; Parisen, Barbara; Parisen, Brent; Pecci, Ernest F.; Popa, Marcia; Reed, Henry; Schroff, Lois; Sparrow, Gregory Scott; Stoller, Ken; Whiting, Charles; Whiting, Claire; Zink, Joan
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1979 1980; Folder 8:5; Baker, Jim; Barker, Malcolm; Bennett, Stephanie; Cayce, Charles Thomas; Clapp, Ann L.; Clapp, Robert O.; Drummond, Richard; Durley, Dryn; Johnston, R.P.; Kohr, Richard; Krajenke, Robert; Kramer, Modenia; O'Connor, Don; Parisen, Barbara; Prochownik, Diane; Puryear, Herbert; Puryear, Meredith; Stevens, Judith; Talamonti, Alessandro; Woods, Steve
  - Box 9
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1980 1981; Folder 9:1; Aberegg, David; Bro, Harmon; Cayce, Charles Thomas; Cayce, Edgar; Cayce, Leslie Goodman; Cerminara, Gina; Church, W.H.; DeSilva, Harry; DeSilva, Sally; Drummond, Richard; Gackenbach, Jane; Henderson, Elizabeth; Irion, J. Everett; Jewell, Michael; Lewis, Kay; O'Connor, Don; O'Malley, George; Owens, Hope; Philpot, Romaine; Puryear, Meredith; Richardson, Dolores; Salerno, Cheryl; Sechrist, Wilfred; Selover, Lila; Smith, Dorothy; Smith, Robert; Sparrow, Gregory Scott; Sugrue, Thomas; Titcomb, Elizabeth; Tomlin, Fred; Tomlin, Mary; Trout, Susan; Tworney, Mary
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1982 1983; Folder 9:2; Adriance, Robert; Ames, Edward; Beck, Pluma; Bro, Harmon; Cayce, Edgar; Church, W.H.; Chute, Rosemary; Davidson, Gordon; Davidson, McLaughlin; Humann, Harvey; Irion, J. Everett; Jeffries, Robert; Kohr, Richard; Krajenke, Robert; Lewis, Kay; Miller, Lynnette; Richardson, Dolores; Rongliang, Zheng; Sanner, Marylyn; Sigma, Rho; Spangler, David; Stryker, Lise; Thurston, Mark
    - A.R.E. Journal, 1983 1984; Folder 9:3; Adriance, Robert; Bro, Harmon; Carson, S.L.; Church, W.H.; Clingerman, Rose; Dennis, Michael; Gibbons, Pam; Grant, Robert; Humann, Harvey; Jahoda, Ursula; La Croix, Mary; Lewis, Kay; Markin, Alexander; Orkin, Kenneth; Pagano, John; Rose, Gary; Sanderfur, E. Glenn; Sanner, Marylyn; Stevens, Judith; Thurston, Mark; Wakester, Amanda
    - A.R.E. Journal; provenance information, 2014; Folder 9:4
    - A.R.E. Journal; reprints, 1969 1976; Folder 9:5
  - Box 10
    - articles, 1932; Folder 10:1; Foerter, A.J.
    - Congress publications, 1932; Folder 10:2; Cayce, Edgar
    - lectures, 1932; Folder 10:3; Cayce, Edgar; Wynne, Esther
    - membership letters, 1932; Folder 10:4; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - articles, 1933; Folder 10:5; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - Congress publications, 1933; Folder 10:6; Bisey, Sunkar; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Cayce, Edgar
    - announcements, 1934; Folder 10:7
    - Congress publications, 1934; Folder 10:8
    - announcements, 1935; Folder 10:9; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - articles, 1935; Folder 10:10; Cayce, Edgar; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - Congress publications, 1935; Folder 10:11
    - membership letters, 1935; Folder 10:12; Cayce, Edgar
    - membership list, 1935; Folder 10:13
    - announcements, 1936; Folder 10:14
    - articles, 1936; Folder 10:15; Moore, Jennie; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - Congress publications, 1936; Folder 10:16; Hardwicke, Henry; Cayce, Gertrude Evans
    - membership letters, 1936; Folder 10:17; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - announcements, 1937; Folder 10:18; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Wynne, Esther; Edmonds, Florence; House, Thomas Burr, Sr.
    - articles, 1937; Folder 10:19; Morrow, Frances Yelden King; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - Congress publications, 1937; Folder 10:20
    - membership letters, 1937; Folder 10:21; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Cayce, Edgar
    - announcements, 1938; Folder 10:22
    - articles, 1938; Folder 10:23; Sugrue, Thomas; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - Congress publications, 1938; Folder 10:24
  - Box 11
    - membership letters, 1938; Folder 11:1; Cayce, Edgar
    - articles, 1939; Folder 11:2; Sugrue, Thomas; Moore, Jennie; Cayce, Edgar; Dell, Louise H.; Ellington, Helen; Harris, Alice; LeNoir, Ruth
    - Congress publications, 1939; Folder 11:3; Cayce, Edgar
    - membership letters, 1939; Folder 11:4; Turner, Gladys Davis
    - announcements, 1940; Folder 11:5
    - articles, 1940; Folder 11:6; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Sugrue, Thomas
    - Congress publications, 1940; Folder 11:7; Smith, Enid Severy; Learned, Leila H.
    - membership letters, 1940; Folder 11:8; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - articles, 1941; Folder 11:9
    - Congress publications, 1941; Folder 11:10
    - articles, 1942; Folder 11:11
    - Congress publications, 1942; Folder 11:12
    - membership letters, 1942; Folder 11:13; Cayce, Edgar
    - articles, 1943; Folder 11:14; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
  - Box 12
    - announcements, 1943; Folder 12:1
    - articles, 1943; Folder 12:2; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - Congress publications, 1943; Folder 12:3
    - pamphlets, 1943; Folder 12:4-12:5; Horton, Evelyn Millicent; Smith, Enid Severy
    - announcements, 1944; Folder 12:6; Turner, Gladys Davis
    - articles, 1944; Folder 12:7; Bro, Harmon
    - Congress publications, 1944; Folder 12:8; Bro, Harmon
    - articles, 1945; Folder 12:9-12:10
  - Box 13
    - Congress publications, 1945; Folder 13:1
    - membership letters, 1945; Folder 13:2
    - announcements, 1946; Folder 13:3
    - articles, 1946; Folder 13:4; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Cerminara, Gina
    - Congress publications, 1946; Folder 13:5
    - membership letters, 1946; Folder 13:6
    - announcements, 1947; Folder 13:7
    - articles, 1947; Folder 13:8; George, Henry, III; White, Walter Louis; Sugrue, Thomas; Norman, H.A.; Cayce, Hugh Lynn
    - Congress publications, 1947; Folder 13:9
    - membership letters, 1947; Folder 13:10; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Helms, Theron
    - announcements, 1948; Folder 13:11